因为AsyncTask是在Activity组件里面被创建  所以它可以
Because it's being created within an Activity, it can be
被很轻松地终止  例如把手机旋转到另一个不同的
terminated as simply as rotating the phone into a different
方向  因此  AsyncTask只能用于
orientation. So, should only ever be used for tasks whose
生命周期被绑定到宿主Activity组件上的  并且在
lifecycle is tied to the host Activity, and is expected
一两秒内就运行完的任务  在移动设备上
to run for only a second or two. On mobile,
即使认为最轻量的网络请求会很快执行完
it's unwise to assume that even the most trivial network
也是非常不明智的。所以一个更好的办法是
access is going to happen quickly. So a better approach
使用一个服务  一个没有用户界面的应用程序组件
would be to use a service. An application component without
被中断的可能性比较小
the UI that's less likely to be
服务可能会使用到不精确的定时提醒任务
interrupted. Possibly scheduled using an inexact repeating alarm.
更佳的是  Android有一个特定的解决方案  叫做
Even better, Android has a specialized solution know
同步适配器  它专门被设计用以
as Sync Adapter. And it's designed especially to schedule
高效地处理后台数据的同步  并尽可能的高效
your background data syncs as efficiently as possible. Better
当然使用Google云消息是更加好的  当服务器端有变化发生时
still would be using Google Cloud Messaging. This lets
它可以用来通知你的同步适配器
you notify your Sync Adapter of changes on the
所以只有当你知道服务器上
server side. So you're only ever initiating network requests
有数据更新的时候，你才需要在App里发起
from your app when you know there's something to
一个网络请求  目前我们只需要尽力
be updated on the server. For now we're concentrating
使我们的应用在前台很好的工作  但是稍后
on making our app work when it's in the foreground. But we'll return to
我们仍然会回过头看看在后台
look at these approaches to invisibly updating
更新你的App的方法
your app from the background a little
目前  只需要记住在我们开发应用的剩余部分时
later. For now, keep in mind that the refresh button and the new thread
刷新按钮以及创建新的线程都只是临时替代方案
solution is just a place holder while we hook up the rest of the app.